[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：让我们从承诺的角度来讨论这个练习，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's talk about this exercise from the perspective of promises,
我们正在学习的一个新工具，试图帮助改进我们解决问题的方式。
a new tool that we're learning to try to help improve the way we solve the problem.
正如我之前提到的，我们的第一步是
Just as I was mentioning before, our first step is to
在getFile函数中创建承诺，好吗？
create the Promise in the getFile function, okay?
所以我们需要归还我们创造的东西，所以新的承诺和
So we're going to need to return what we create, so new Promise and
我们的承诺函数将收到解决和拒绝。
our Promise function is gonna receive a resolve and a reject.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在我们需要立即进行fakeAjax调用。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now we need to make the fakeAjax call right away.
因此，让我们使用文件名进行fakeAjax调用。
So let's make the fakeAjax call with our filename.
您认为我们应该为fakeAjax提供什么回调？
And what callback do you suppose we should provide to fakeAjax?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：解析函数，非常简单，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The resolve functions, pretty straightforward, right?
现在我们没有考虑错误，所以实际上为了简单起见，
Now here we're not taking care of errors, so actually just to keep things simple,
我将不再考虑拒绝，因为我们不关心错误情况
I'm going to just leave off the reject because we don't care about the error case
但是当然，如果我们的Ajax函数具有处理错误的能力，
but of course, if our Ajax function had the ability to handle errors,
我们可以通过拒绝函数连接错误处理。
we could wire up that error handling through the reject function.
所以伪造Ajax文件并解决，非常简单。
So fakeAjax file and resolve, pretty straightforward.
关于这部分有什么问题吗？
Any questions about that part?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：在现实生活中，我们不必创建承诺对象
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: In the real life situation, we don't have to create a promise object
无论我们将得到什么[INAUDIBLE]，如果它被称为[INAUDIBLE]，
of whatever we are going to get [INAUDIBLE] should it be called,
我们将给我们一个承诺&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：所以问题是，在
we're going to give us a promise &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So the question is, in
现实生活中，我们是不是必须做出自己的承诺，而答案是有时候。
real life, are we gonna have to make our own promises and the answer is sometimes.
因为有时候，你会调用一个已经知道承诺的实用程序，并且
Because sometimes, you're going to call a utility that is already promise aware and
给你一个很好的承诺。
gives you a great promise.
有时你会调用实用程序，它会给你一些类似于
Sometimes you're gonna call the utility that gives you something that's kinda like
一个承诺，但它并不是真正的，在承诺的世界里，我们称其为athable和
a promise, but it isn't really and in the promise world, we call that athenable and
然后你需要做出一个承诺来包裹它。
then you're gonna need to make a promise that wraps around it.
有时您将有一个回调实用程序，它甚至不是远程的
Sometimes you're going to have a callback utility that's not even remotely
承诺意识，以及
promise aware, and
你需要把它改写成一个承诺，这就是我们在这里所做的。
you're gonna need to adapt that to a promise, which is what we're doing here.
我们有一个实用程序，它不知道承诺，我们正在修改它。
We have a utility that doesn't know about promises and we're adapting it.
这种模式称为提升。
This pattern is called lifting.
我们正在fakeAjax函数之上创建一个Promise Aware实用程序。
We are creating a promise aware utility on top of the fakeAjax function.
事实上，承诺图书馆确实提供了
And in fact Promise libraries do offer
将为您进行自动提升的实用程序。
utilities that will do automatic lifting for you.
他们将创建我们在这里所做的包装器模式
They will create this wrapper pattern that we're doing here and
我们是手动做的，所以我们可以举例说明，但是
we're doing it manually, so we can illustrate, but
我们将看到Promise实用程序库，它们这样做是为了
we'll see that Promise utilities libraries out there, they do this for
我们是因为你不想自己在适应过程中绊倒。
us because you don't want to be tripping over doing that adaptation yourself.
这是一个可重复的模式，它属于一个库。
That's a repeatable pattern, it belongs in a library.
好的，所以我们仍然需要调用getFile函数三次。
Okay, so we still want to call the getFile function three times.
就像Thunks一样
Just like with Thunks,
在这个案子里我们会拿回一些东西他们会是承诺。
we're gonna get something back in this case they're gonna be promises.
我要说p1=getFile(“file1”)和
I'm gonna say p1 = getFile ("file1") and
P2=getFile(“File2”)和
p2 = getFile("file2") and
p3=getFile(“file3”)。
p3 = getFile("file3").
太好了，太棒了。
Great, awesome.
所以我们同时打了这三个电话。
So we've made those three calls in parallel.
我们该拿他们怎么办？
What are we going to do with them?
我们如何对他们的反应进行排序？
How are we going to sequence their responses?
这就是这个练习的重点，对回答进行排序。
That's the whole point of this exercise, sequencing the responses.
所以，让我们一起考虑一下我们的反应顺序。
So, let's think about sequencing our responses together.
我们知道p1会在某个时候结束。
We know that p1 is at some point gonna finish.
我们假设在这个系统中，承诺总是会解决的，所以
We're assuming in this system, that the promise always resolves, so
在某种程度上，它将会结束。
at some point, its going to finish.
所以为了响应这个结束，我们可以简单地说p1，then。
So to respond to that finishing, we can simply say p1.then.
现在我们知道来自p1的成功处理程序将接收输出
Now we know that the success handler from p1 is going to receive the output
我们给它的就像这里，我们的承诺，结果函数将得到
that we gave it just like up here, our Promise that result functions going to get
通过响应文本，然后传播到承诺链中。
past the response text and that will then propagate into the Promise chain.
所以我们这里需要的是一个可以接收文本和
So what we need here is a function that can receive the text and
将其打印出来，我们就有了一个名为output的实用程序。
print it out and we have a utility called output.
所以我们可以这样做，但是
So we could do it like that but
结果是更容易，因为我们已经有了一个实用程序
it turns out even easier since we have a utility that already has that
调用签名，我们只需将引用传递给输出函数即可。
call signature, we can just simply pass a reference to the output function.
不叫它，不要把括号放在里面。
Not calling it, don't put the parenthesis in there.
您需要将对该函数的引用传递到链中。
You wanna pass a reference to that function into the chain.
在这里，现在我想提出一个关于承诺链的非常重要的观点
Here, and now I want to make a really important point about Promise chains
从风格和可读性的角度来看。
from a style and readability perspective.
你会看到许诺的无数例子
You'll see tons and tons of examples of promises where
说明承诺链的方式是使用内联函数表达式。
the way the promise chains are illustrated is to use inline function expressions.
事实上，这是人们喜欢去的地方之一
In fact, this is one of the favorite places that people like to
取出ES6错误函数并将其作为内联函数表达式。
pull out ES6 error functions and put them as inline function expressions.
我觉得这是个糟糕的主意
I think this is a terrible idea,
将内联函数表达式放在您的承诺链上。
to put inline function expressions all over your Promise chains.
使用函数声明。
Use function declarations.
承诺链的要点，
The point of a Promise chain,
如果它有任何一点，从可读性的角度来看，唯一的
if it has any point at all, from a readability perspective, the only
可读性观点是，您应该能够轻松地垂直向下扫描和
readability perspective is that you should be able to easily vertically scan down and
理解流控制是什么，就像我们在那个伪代码中所做的那样。
understand what the flow control is like we did in that pseudo code.
如果您的链中散布着各种内联函数表达式和
If your chain is littered with all kinds of inline function expressions and
怪异之类的东西，
weirdness and stuff like that,
您已经完全失去了Promise链的所有可读性优势。
you've completely lost all the readability advantages of the Promise chain.
因此，当我有一个函数时，我更喜欢使用它。
So I prefer to use a function when I have one.
这并不意味着您永远不会使用函数表达式，但是
That doesn't mean you won't ever use a function expression, but
我会说如果有机会不使用一个表达式
I'm gonna say if there's an opportunity to not use an expression and
而是做一份声明，最好是那样，好吗？
instead do a declaration, it's better to go that way, okay?
好的现在，我们说的是无论一个人完成了什么承诺，我们都想输出它。
All right now, what we've said is whatever Promise one finishes, we wanna output it.
我们已经保证了诺言一，
We have ensured that the Promise one,
文件一的内容是要打印的第一件事。
that the file one contents are the first thing to be printed.
所以我们已经确保了这是如何工作的。
So we've ensured just by way of how this works.
我们知道一个事实，我们将会像Thunks一样按顺序打印。
We know for a fact that we're going to be printing in order just like with Thunks.
下一步是什么？
What's the next step?
你的本能可能会说我知道
Well your instinct might be to say well I know that the way to
一起改变一些诺言，就是从一个诺言到另一个诺言的回报。
change some promises together, is to return one promise from another promise.
所以对我们来说，传递第二次承诺似乎很有吸引力
So it would seem very attractive for us to just pass in Promise two
进入链条，使它在它的电线和衰弱。
into the chain and make it so that it wires it in and wanes.
我希望承诺就是这样起作用的。
And I wish that's how Promises worked.
我希望你能给当时的方法传递一个承诺
I wish you could pass a Promise in to the then method and
让它自动知道要做什么。
have it automatically know what to do.
不幸的是，承诺没有这种功能。
Unfortunately, Promises don't have that feature.
所以你必须传入一个返回承诺的函数。
So you have to pass in a function that returns that Promise.
再举一个例子，人们一直在使用错误函数。
Again, an example where people use error functions all the time.
在这种情况下，我会将其转换为函数声明吗？
Is this a case where I'd make that into a function declaration?
也许吧。
Perhaps.
但为了我们的目的，只是为了保持干净，
But for our purposes, just to keep things clean,
我将使用函数表达式，但仅仅是告诫，
I'm going to use the function expressions, but just with the admonition,
您希望尽量减少流控制中的表达式数量。
you want to try to minimize the amount of expressions in your flow control.
如果你要拥有他们，请让他们像一个衬里。
And if you're gonna have them, by goodness please make them like one liners.
如果链中有5，10，15，100行内嵌表达式，
If you have 5, 10, 15, 100 line inline expressions inside of your chains,
这是个糟糕的主意好吗？
that's a terrible idea, okay?
但是我们已经从链条中返回了P 2，这意味着
But we've returned P two from the chain which means
这里发生的下一步将神奇地等待P2。
that the very next step that happens here is gonna magically be waiting on P two.
大家都看到了吗？
Does everybody see that?
那么，在P两个完成后我们想做什么？
So what do we want to do after P two finishes?
你想再输出一次。
You wanna output again.
然后你可能会猜到接下来会发生什么。
And then you can probably guess what happens next right.
.然后函数，返回p3和
.then function, return p3 and
然后，然后输出。
then .then output.
最后。然后，只是
And finally .then, just for
完整性考虑与其他例子，输出一个完整的消息。
completeness sake with the other examples, output a complete message.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我们的流控制使用承诺。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: There's our flow control using promises.
它是垂直定向的，而不是嵌套在一起的，
It's vertically oriented rather than being nested together,
当然增加了一点可读性因素。
certainly has increased the readability factor by a bit.
但这是所发生的事情中最不重要的部分。
But that's the least important part of what's happened.
我们还介绍了所有的理智和
We've also introduced all of the sanity and
来自承诺机制的信任。
trust that comes from the Promise mechanism.
我们可以相信，如果fakeAjax实用程序不知何故行为不当或恶意，或者
We can trust that if that fakeAjax utility somehow misbehaves or is malicious or
是被劫持了还是什么，我们知道无论它做什么，
is hijacked or whatever, we know that no matter what it does,
如果它调用了50，000次，我们只是
if it calls that resolve 50,000 times, we're only
会得到一次通知，因为承诺系统就是这样建立的。
gonna get notified once because that's the way the Promise system is built.
所以我们已经把我们的信任从一些不可信任的第三方
So we've shifted our trust from some untrustable third party
变成一个非常可信的系统，事实上，一个内置在语言中的系统。
into a very trustable system, in fact, one that's built into the language.
但即使不是，我们也知道我们可以审计和
But even if it wasn't, we know we can audit and
相信承诺系统会做它应该做的事情。
trust the Promise system to do what its supposed to do.